<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-08-16T17:53:17+05:30</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">lc-research</title><subtitle>Welcome to lc-research.com</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Metabolomics: A Potential Path to Early Detection of Terminal Diseases</title><link href="/metabolomics/2018/02/24/metabolomics.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Metabolomics: A Potential Path to Early Detection of Terminal Diseases" /><published>2018-02-24T18:50:15+05:30</published><updated>2018-02-24T18:50:15+05:30</updated><id>/metabolomics/2018/02/24/metabolomics</id><content type="html" xml:base="/metabolomics/2018/02/24/metabolomics.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/cancer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cancer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;lead&quot; style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Early detection is a misnomer. At the time of diagnosis, a solid tumor developing in the breast, colon, lung, or prostate has grown to 1 cm in size and contains 1 billion cells. The average time for this growth to reach a detectable size is 10 years. Cancer destined to spread to other vital organs has already done so.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;We all are made up of cells. With a few exceptions, each of our body’s hundred trillion cells contains a copy of our genome: the entire set of hereditary instructions for building and functioning of an organism. This instruction set is made up of long DNA molecules. The DNA contains the recipes for making proteins. Proteins are the workhorse molecules of cells. They are the building materials for many structures in the cell. They take part in all sorts of biological functions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;With the help of proteins, cells make and alter a large number of small molecules through a series of chemical reactions. Those small molecules (usually smaller than 1000 Daltons) are known as metabolites. The entire set of metabolites in an organism is known as its metabolome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;The metabolome is the closest link to the observable characteristics and traits of an organism (also known as phenotype). Metabolomics is the scientific study of chemical processes involving these metabolites. Elevation of certain types of metabolites or presence of unusual metabolites could be an indicator of a hidden disease. These metabolomics clues may lead to much earlier diagnosis of terminal diseases such as cancers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Dr. Lochana C. Menikarachchi</name><email>lochanac@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">Early detection is a misnomer. At the time of diagnosis, a solid tumor developing in the breast, colon, lung, or prostate has grown to 1 cm in size and contains 1 billion cells. The average time for this growth to reach a detectable size is 10 years. Cancer destined to spread to other vital organs has already done so. We all are made up of cells. With a few exceptions, each of our body’s hundred trillion cells contains a copy of our genome: the entire set of hereditary instructions for building and functioning of an organism. This instruction set is made up of long DNA molecules. The DNA contains the recipes for making proteins. Proteins are the workhorse molecules of cells. They are the building materials for many structures in the cell. They take part in all sorts of biological functions. With the help of proteins, cells make and alter a large number of small molecules through a series of chemical reactions. Those small molecules (usually smaller than 1000 Daltons) are known as metabolites. The entire set of metabolites in an organism is known as its metabolome. The metabolome is the closest link to the observable characteristics and traits of an organism (also known as phenotype). Metabolomics is the scientific study of chemical processes involving these metabolites. Elevation of certain types of metabolites or presence of unusual metabolites could be an indicator of a hidden disease. These metabolomics clues may lead to much earlier diagnosis of terminal diseases such as cancers.</summary></entry></feed>