<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LC-Research</title>
    <link>https://lc-research.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LC-Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lc-research.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connecting TWS Earbuds to Any TV or Projector</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/twstotv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/twstotv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there anyway to watch movies on the big screen (TV or projector) without disturbing others? Can two people share  wireless audio at the same time? What about TWS earbuds? Can we use them with our TVs?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>WEBSITE DISCLAIMER The information provided by LC-Research (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”) on https://lc-research.com (the “Site”) is for general informational purposes only. All information on the Site is provided in good faith, however we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability, or completeness of any information on the Site.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCE SHALL WE HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF THE SITE OR RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE SITE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>At LC-Research, accessible from lc-research.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by LC-Research and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in LC-Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Raspberry Pi Media Server</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/minidlna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/minidlna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got a whole bunch of movies, audio files and photos on my laptop. I am tired of copying these files to other devices at home. Is there anyway to keep them in one location and stream to all of my TVs, mobile phones, tablets and computers on the home network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Glide App</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/glide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/glide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I need to develop a personal mobile app that works on android. But, I don&amp;rsquo;t have much time on hand or coding skills required. I hear there are platforms that can turn spreadsheets into mobile apps. Is it even possible? How long would it take to build one from scratch?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Rid of ._ and .DS_Store Files</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/mactowin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/mactowin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just got some folders from a Mac user. I see hundreds of ._ files and .DS_Store files all over my file system. Is it safe to delete these files? How can I get rid of them quickly?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/about/</guid>
      <description>There are plenty of blogs on tech and gadgets. Engadget, Gizmodo, C|net, you name it. Why do we need another one?
I use all sorts of technologies to make my life easier. I thoroughly research products before I buy them. Once in a while, when something fails, I need to go back and fix something or reconfigure some software that I setup ages ago. The only problem is keeping everything in my memory, especially those that involve multiple steps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
