<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on LC-Research</title>
    <link>https://lc-research.com/categories/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on LC-Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lc-research.com/categories/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connecting TWS Earbuds to Any TV or Projector</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/twstotv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/twstotv/</guid>
      <description>Since my son&amp;rsquo;s arrival, watching a TV show or a movie on a TV became a near impossible task. Our little guy seemed to have a super hearing that could detect even inaudible footsteps miles away. He would wake up to tiniest of tiny sounds. We had no choice but to put watching movies on big screen to the back burner. My poor wife resort to watching short video clips on her mobile phone with a wired earphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Raspberry Pi Media Server</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/minidlna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/minidlna/</guid>
      <description>It has been a little over three years since I have setup a Raspberry Pi based wireless media server. This little media server has done a great job and it continues to function flawlessly serving many DLNA clients in the home network including one 3D projector, several mobile phones, tablets, PCs and Macs. I needed an always on light weight media server that can serve all of my DLNA compliant devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Rid of ._ and .DS_Store Files</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/mactowin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/mactowin/</guid>
      <description>You may be a Windows user who received a bunch of folders from a work colleague who is using a Mac. Or you may be frequently sharing files between a Mac and a Windows computer. Or you may be copying files from your Mac to USB sticks. Whatever the use case, you must have encountered the mystical and annoying ._ files.
What exactly are these files? How do you get rid of them?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
