<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorials on LC-Research</title>
    <link>https://lc-research.com/categories/tutorials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorials on LC-Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 16:13:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lc-research.com/categories/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Care for Your Laptop&#39;s Battery</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/laptopbattery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 16:13:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/laptopbattery/</guid>
      <description>Almost all mobile computers have a built-in lithium-ion battery. Batteries that seem to last forever at the beginning hold less and less charge as they age. Is there anyway to delay the degradation of lithium batteries? What practices could potentially prolong or harm the lithium batteries found in everyday laptops? This post aims to shed some light on this topic by debunking common battery myths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Control of Your Passwords with Bitwarden</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/bitwarden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/bitwarden/</guid>
      <description>Having to deal with many passwords is a fact of life. A password manager like Bitwarden can ease the burden of inventing and remembering passwords. This step-by-step tutorial explains how to setup Bitwarden with its browser extension for Chrome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting TWS Earbuds to Any TV or Projector</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/twstotv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/twstotv/</guid>
      <description>How wonderful is it to have your TV audio streamed to your wireless earbuds? This post shows you how you can connect two pairs of TWS earbuds or bluetooth headsets with any TV or projector. Finally, two can watch a movie on the big screen without disturbing others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Raspberry Pi Media Server</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/minidlna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/minidlna/</guid>
      <description>Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be nice to store all of your media files in one location and stream them to any device on your home network? An inexpensive Raspberry Pi and a couple of USB sticks can get the job done! This post guides you through all the steps required, step by step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Rid of ._ and .DS_Store Files</title>
      <link>https://lc-research.com/blog/mactowin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lc-research.com/blog/mactowin/</guid>
      <description>When you  transfer files and folders from Macs to PCs and USB sticks a whole bunch of ._ files and .DS_Store files are generated. While there is no way to prevent this from happening, there is an easy way to get rid of these pesky files. This post shows you how.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
